pageresource.com 2002-02-05

# Privacy Statement for PageResource.Com

The Web Design Resource has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: PageResource.Com. 

Be sure to view our **Children's Privacy Policy**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. 

This site contains links to other sites. **PageResource.Com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Our site uses a [contact form](http://www.pageresource.com/contact.htm) and a site submission form for customers to request information, return links, and services. In these forms, we collect visitor's contact information (like name, email address, and site addresses). The customer's contact information is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. If a visitor submits a web site for a link review, the site address, title, and description provided may be posted on the appropriate pages. A visitor's e-mail address is not shared with or sold to any third parties. If you do not want us to know any of the information above, do not submit either form to us. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Our occasional online surveys ask visitors for demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. We do not share a visitor's individual information. 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. Ads may contain cookies, and appear to be coming from our site, but in reality they are coming from our partners who are serving ads on our site. Our site does not use cookies, except in the discussion forums. We do not have access to any information about you from cookies you might receive while visiting our site. Some customer data is shared with the advertising companies on an aggregate basis. You can view the privacy policies of the advertising companies we use through the links below: 

The Web Design Resource works with a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how About.com manages the privacy information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to:   
<http://home.about.com/gi/pages/privacy.htm>

The Web Design Resource works with a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how Tribal Fusion manages the privacy information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to:   
<http://www.tribalfusion.com/www/about/privacy.html>

The Web Design Resource works with a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how Burst! Media manages the privacy information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to:   
<http://www.burstmedia.com/release/privacy.asp>

The Web Design Resource works with a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how ValueClick manages the privacy information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to:   
<http://valueclick.com/privacy.html>

### Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, guest books, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

### Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [john@pageresource.com](mailto:john@pageresource.com)

### Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. You can send email to [john@pageresource.com](mailto:john@pageresource.com)

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact John Pollock The Web Design Resource 936-295-4567 john@pageresource.com

* * *

This statement was generated with help from the Privacy Statement Wizard at: <http://www.truste.org/>. We made the proper adjustments to it to reflect our site's information. The rest was written by the wizard. 

\--------------------  
Copyright © 1997-2001 [The Web Design Resource](http://www.pageresource.com/). All rights reserved. 
The Web Design Resource has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: PageResource.Com. 

Be sure to view our **Children's Privacy Policy**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. 

This site contains links to other sites. **PageResource.Com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Our site uses a [contact form](http://www.pageresource.com/contact.htm) and a site submission form for customers to request information, return links, and services. In these forms, we collect visitor's contact information (like name, email address, and site addresses). The customer's contact information is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. If a visitor submits a web site for a link review, the site address, title, and description provided may be posted on the appropriate pages. A visitor's e-mail address is not shared with or sold to any third parties. If you do not want us to know any of the information above, do not submit either form to us. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Our occasional online surveys ask visitors for demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. We do not share a visitor's individual information. 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. Ads may contain cookies, and appear to be coming from our site, but in reality they are coming from our partners who are serving ads on our site. Our site does not use cookies, except in the discussion forums. We do not have access to any information about you from cookies you might receive while visiting our site. Some customer data is shared with the advertising companies on an aggregate basis. You can view the privacy policies of the advertising companies we use through the links below: 

The Web Design Resource works with a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how About.com manages the privacy information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to:   
<http://home.about.com/gi/pages/privacy.htm>

The Web Design Resource works with a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how Tribal Fusion manages the privacy information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to:   
<http://www.tribalfusion.com/www/about/privacy.html>

The Web Design Resource works with a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how Burst! Media manages the privacy information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to:   
<http://www.burstmedia.com/release/privacy.asp>

The Web Design Resource works with a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how ValueClick manages the privacy information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to:   
<http://valueclick.com/privacy.html>

### Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, guest books, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

### Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [john@pageresource.com](mailto:john@pageresource.com)

### Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. You can send email to [john@pageresource.com](mailto:john@pageresource.com)

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact John Pollock The Web Design Resource 936-295-4567 john@pageresource.com

* * *

This statement was generated with help from the Privacy Statement Wizard at: <http://www.truste.org/>. We made the proper adjustments to it to reflect our site's information. The rest was written by the wizard. 

\--------------------  
Copyright © 1997-2001 [The Web Design Resource](http://www.pageresource.com/). All rights reserved.
